http://allcursors.com/terms.php


AllCursors Terms of Service

AllCursors is a downloadable software application including a browser add-on ("Product") distributed by AllCursors and available at www.allcursors.com ("Website"). AllCursors is a free application that lets you customize your web browsing cursor on any web page you visit.

PLEASE READ THIS AGREEMENT THROUGHLY, AS IT CONTAINS IMPORTANT INFORMATION REGARDING YOUR LEGAL RIGHTS, REMEDIES AND OBLIGATIONS.

By accessing or using the Website, downloading or using AllCursors, you accept and agree to the requirements of the Terms of Service without any reservations, alterations, additions or omissions. If you do not agree to any provisions confined in the Terms of Service, you are not authorized to use the Website or the Application. You may be denied access to the Website and the Application with or without notice to you, if you do not comply with any provisions of the Terms of Service.
Advertising

AllCursors is supported by advertising, which may include display, in-text and/or interstitial ads. Users may see additional display ads on websites that the product runs on or adds functionality to. You will see approximately 1 display ad per page on content sites; however, at times as many as 5 display advertisements per page. On search engines there may be a search app, which may display 3 text ads beneath the application. In addition, topics or keyword phrases are automatically matched and products or services relevant to those topics or keyword phrases will appear on the webpage as a double underline.

These ads will be recognized as originating from AllCursors. The user will not be shown any material that may be considered pornographic, promotes violence or the use of firearms and contains obscene language. Ad optimizers will monitor the traffic and provide an ad inspector tool for quality assurance.
Third Party Sites

The Website and AllCursors may contain links to third party sites or resources that are not owned or controlled by Product. Product has no control over and assumes no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, practices or availability of any third party sites. You are and remain subject to the policies of those third parties where applicable. By using the Website and AllCursors you expressly relieve AllCursors from any and all liability (direct or indirect) arising from your use of any share functionality or third-party site.
A Special Note for Parents and Guardians

The Product respects the U.S Children's Online Privacy Protection (COPPA) Act of 1998 and the guidelines of the Children's Advertising Review Unit (CARU) of the Council of Better Business Bureau, Inc. in each of its websites for children. You can help by spending time online with your children and monitoring your children's online use. Please help us protect your child's privacy by instructing them never to provide personal information on this website or any other without your permission. Furthermore, children will not be shown

If you are under 18, please be sure to read this policy with your parents or legal guardians and ask questions about things you do not understand.
Settings

AllCursors will be automatically enabled on IE, Firefox and Chrome following installation. These settings may be changed at any time, but doing so may interfere with the operation of AllCursors. Additionally, optional offers will be presented to the User for download. All products selected will be downloaded to a temp directory, and installed automatically.
Uninstall Instructions

To uninstall from any of the supported browsers go to the Windows Start Menu and then to Control Panel. Under programs click on uninstall a program. Navigate and click on AllCursors. Click on Uninstall/Change.

For more detailed uninstall instructions, feel free to visit the uninstall section on our About page.
Additional Features and Updates to Terms and Service

When AllCursors has new added functionality to the app or we have edited our Terms and Service, we will provide a notice to you and what upgrades are available and what has changed in our Terms and Service. We will not implement the upgrades until you have consented. If you do not want the upgrades or disagree with the new terms, we will provide you with an option to uninstall.
Prevention

So that the Website and AllCursors are available for all users to enjoy, you may not, and hereby represent, warrant and pledge that you will not or permit or enable a third party to:

Access or attempt to access any of the Services by use of an automated tool to operate the Services (scripts, etc.); or

Use the Website or AllCursors in a way that: Violates the terms of the Terms of Service;

Is unlawful, infringing, harmful, threatening, abusive, obscene, invasive of another's privacy, hateful, fraudulent or malicious;

Involves the transmission of "junk mail", "chain letters", or unsolicited mass mailing or "spamming";

Involves the sending of any virus, Trojan horse, worm, harmful code, shutdown mechanism or similar mechanism;

Promotes information that you know is false, misleading, or promotes illegal activities or conduct;

Solicits passwords, or personal identifying information

Interferes with or disrupts the Website, AllCursors
Intellectual Property Grant of License

AllCursors grants you a non-exclusive, non-transferable, worldwide, revocable license to access and use of the Website and AllCursors in accordance with the terms set forth in the Terms of Service. The Website and AllCursors are made available to you for your non-commercial use only. You need to obtain our permission if you want (i) to sell, distribute, license or in any other way exploit, in whole or in part, the Services, the use of the Website or the AllCursors (including by way of a bundle with other products and/or services).
Reservation of Rights

AllCursors reserves all right, title and interest not expressly granted under this license to the fullest extent possible under applicable laws. You may not sublicense, assign, or transfer the license granted to you under the Terms of Service, and any attempt to sublicense, assign, or transfer any part of your rights under the Terms of Service is void. Limitation of Liability General Disclaimer TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, IN NO EVENT WILL PRODUCT, ITS AFFILIATES OR AGENTS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES OR LOSSES OF ANY KIND AND BASED ON ANY THEORY OF LAW, EQUITY, CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE ARISING FROM YOUR USE OR INABILITY TO USE THE SITE OR THE SOFTWARE, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DAMAGES TO YOUR SYSTEMS AND/OR YOUR SOFTWARE AND/OR DATA, COMPUTER FAILURE OR MALFUNCTION, COMPUTER VIRUS TRANSMISSION, PERFORMANCE DELAYS OR COMMUNICATION FAILURES OR SECURITY BREACHES.
No Warranty

YOU EXPRESSLY AGREE THAT THE USE OF THE SITE AND THE SOFTWARE ARE AT YOUR OWN RISK. THE SITE AND THE SOFTWARE ARE PROVIDED ON AN 'AS-IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO, ANY IMPLIED WARRANTY OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, WARRANTIES OF NON-INFRINGEMENT AND FREEDOM FROM VIRUSES, AND ANY WARRANTY IMPLIED THROUGH COURSE OF PERFORMANCE, COURSE OF DEALING, OR USAGE OF TRADE. WITHOUT LIMITING THE FOREGOING, BUT TO BE CLEAR, PRODUCT NEITHER WARRANTS NOR WILL REPRESENT THAT YOUR USE OF SITE MATERIALS WILL NOT INFRINGE RIGHTS OF THIRD PARTIES. SOME JURISDICTIONS MAY NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OF IMPLIED WARRANTIES, SO SOME OR ALL OF THE ABOVE EXCLUSION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.
Termination of Use

You agree that we may, in our sole discretion, terminate or suspend your access to all or part of the site with or without notice and for any reason, including, without limitation, breach of these Terms of Use. Any suspected fraudulent, abusive or illegal activity may be grounds for terminating your relationship and may be referred to appropriate law enforcement authorities.

Upon termination or suspension, regardless of the reasons therefore, your right to use the services available on this site immediately ceases, and you acknowledge and agree that we may immediately deactivate or delete your account and all related information and files in your account and/or bar any further access to such files or this site. We shall not be liable to you or any third party for any claims or damages arising out of any termination or suspension or any other actions taken by us in connection with such termination or suspension. General The failure to exercise or enforce any right or provision of this Agreement will not operate as a waiver of such right or provision. The section titles in this Agreement are for convenience only and have no legal or contractual effect. This Agreement operates to the fullest extent permissible by law. If any provision of this Agreement is unlawful, void or unenforceable, that provision is deemed severable from this Agreement and does not affect the validity and enforceability of any remaining provisions. PII Collection If you would like access to your personal information to collect, update, or delete it, please contact us as described below:
AllCursors Physical Mail Address:

717-D Fellowship Road,
Mount Laurel, NJ 08054
Contact Information

If you notice that any user is violating these Terms of Use, please contact us at allcursors@gmail.com
